Thank you for shopping at the SafeGraph Shop!

* DOCUMENTATION and DATA SCHEMAS are at https://docs.safegraph.com/docs

* If you need help parsing the JSON columns or using the data in ESRI, please see our FAQs at https://docs.safegraph.com/docs/faqs

* If you have any questions or need technical support, please join our Slack community for assistance at https://www.safegraph.com/community

* Happy exploring!